<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<resources>

    <string name="hello">Hello World, Mainactivity!</string>
    <string name="s1">Ring Mode:</string>
    <string name="s3i">Battery Eye:</string>
    <string name="s3id">A siren is triggered when battery charge match with the pre-defined level(0-100%) you saved.Then you can unplug mobile to stop Siren</string>
<string name="howtotext1"> Based on the code you have saved .you will be able to remotely change mode of your mobile by sending that particular code as SMS to your mobile </string>

    <string name="app_name">RingEye </string>
    <string name="app_name1">RingMode </string>

<string name="BatteryEye">BatteryEye</string>
    <string name="Aboutus">About Us</string >
    <color name="t">#95dd69</color>

    <string name="bteye"> Set the level you want and click Save .</string>
    <string name="bteye1">To stop the Siren either click stop button or unplug your mobile from USB/Charger</string>
<string name="bteye2">To turn off battery eye set level to Zero and save</string>
    <string name="Aboutme">About Us</string>
   <string name="AboutRingMode">Ring Mode is a basic utility which helps you remotely change the ringing mode of
       your mobile from silent/vibrate to loud. You can do this by sending a code(Not Case-Sensitive) as an SMS to your mobile phone from any other mobile . </string>

<string name="AboutBatteryEye">
Battery Eye is a battery monitoring system. You can set a desired level between (0-100%).
    A Siren is triggered when your battery reaches the desired level. This works when mobile is plugged in with USB/phone charger. </string>
<string name="note">
            If you find RingEye App useful, please do rate and comment as they are very valuable to us and help us improve our offerings.

 </string >

   <string name="Suggestion">
       Compliments and bug pointers can be sent to ringmode.batteryeye@gmail.com. Thanks :)  </string>
    <string name="bt1">jhjhjjjjjjjjjjjjj</string>

    <string name="topicmain">Enter Codes for each Textbox and click on Save.
        These codes you need to remember.</string>

</resources>

